Resume 2/4/21, 6:48 PM

PATRICIA ATTAH DATA SCIENTIST

Summary

Current graduate student in data science with a major in machine learning, and statistical background including understanding of hypothesis testing, confidence intervals PCA, LDA and time series and experience with python, R, SAS and SQL. Applied knowledge of data processing, data mining and machine learning algorithms to solve practical business problems and find data driven solutions to increase efficiency.

Employment

Springboard Online Student May 2020 to Jan. 2021

Springboard Data Science Career Track - Student

Description: 550+ hours of hands-on course material, with 1:1 industry expert mentor, oversight, and completion of 2 in-depth capstone projects. Mastered skills in Python, SQL, data analysis, data visualization, hypothesis testing, and machine learning.

Jacobs Engineering Structural Designer Dallas Texas Feb. 2019 to Current

Design of structural building framework, substructure and superstructure. Elements include foundation, framework and roof.

- Used critical thinking to ensure adequate design.
- Applied problem solving skills for inconsistencies during design.
- Developed deep understanding of software to produce desired results.
- Ensured design was well detailed, accurate and clear for use.

Projects

Stock Prediction ARIMA Vs LSTM

Dec. 2020 to Dec. 2020

Comparison of neural network to machine learning algorithms for prediction of stock using the LSTM and ARIMA models.

Correlation between heart disease and certain Sept. 2020 to Nov. 2020

machine learning classification model that uses several different algorithms tons which best predicts the outcome of heartsease.

Life Expectancy Predictive model Aug. 2020 to Sept. 2020

Creation of predictive model for the life expectancy with regression using various socioeconomic factors.

Records database design

June 2020 to July 2020

Relational database design using SQL

Housing Price Prediction

June 2020 to June 2020

Contact

- **▼** trishattah@gmail.com
- https://github.com/trishattah/SB-

DataScience-Track

2147808010

♥ www.linkedin.com/in/patriciaattah

Skills

Machine Learning

Data Visualisation

Big Data

Data Mining

Problem solving

Python

SAS

R

SOL

Data ta Wrangling

Education

SMU May 2020 to Current
Masters Data Science 2021

Spring Jan. 2020 to Dec. 2020

Certificate Data science 2020

University of May 2016 to Texas Arlington Dec. 2018
Masters Civil Engineering
2018

Page 1 of 2